Your Excellency is awake.
سعادتك مستيقظ.
You saved me again.
لقد أنقذتني مرة أخرى.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
I won't let you get hurt.
لن أدعك تتأذى.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
how is my senior brother?
كيف حال اخي الاكبر
Bitter tricks can't kill anyone.
الحيل المرة لا تقتل أحدا.
How can you say that about him?
كيف يمكنك قول ذلك عنه؟
After Master left,
بعد مغادرة السيد ،
I only have Senior Brother left.
لم يبق سوى الأخ الأكبر.
I don't want anything to happen to him.
لا أريد أن يحدث له أي شيء.
What if I say he's lying to you?
ماذا لو قلت أنه يكذب عليك؟
He's not that kind of person.
إنه ليس هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
I'll go check on him.
سأذهب للتحقق منه.
Sir,
سيد،
don't go!
لا تذهب!
what is it?
ما هذا؟
A thief broke into
اقتحم لص
the restless old State Preceptor's room.
غرفة مدير الدولة القديم المضطرب.
What?
ماذا؟
Did you find the thief?
هل وجدت اللص؟
The thief was so cunning that he got away.
كان اللص ماكرًا لدرجة أنه أفلت.
Fortunately, I didn't lose anything valuable,
لحسن الحظ ، لم أفقد أي شيء ذي قيمة ،
just some calligraphy and paintings by the old State Preceptor,
فقط بعض الخط واللوحات لمدير الدولة القديم ،
He seems to be a petty thief who doesn't know the goods.
يبدو أنه لص تافه لا يعرف البضاعة.
Master's calligraphy and painting are priceless to me.
فن الخط والرسم لا يقدران بثمن بالنسبة لي.
Send someone to find out immediately.
أرسل شخصًا ما لمعرفة ذلك على الفور.
Yes.
نعم.
Why is this scent so familiar?
لماذا هذه الرائحة مألوفة جدا؟
You are the merman.
أنت الحوري.
Fu Su
فو سو
Fusu left early in the morning.
غادر فوسو في الصباح الباكر.
Chen Moxi,
تشين موكسي
it's her.
انها هي.
You've been away for a long time,
لقد كنت بعيدا لفترة طويلة ،
don't forget who you are.
لا تنسى من أنت.
I heard that
سمعت ان
the girl from Tian Si Fang,
الفتاة من Tian Si Fang ،
You gave yourself away.
لقد أعطيت نفسك بعيدا.
Then just kill them.
ثم اقتلهم فقط.
Don't get emotional.
لا تكن عاطفيًا.
Don't forget why you came to Qin State.
لا تنس لماذا أتيت إلى ولاية تشين.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
you'll be poisoned to death at any time.
سوف تتسمم حتى الموت في أي وقت.
Mo Xi can't be a spy. It must be a frame-up.
لا يمكن أن يكون Mo Xi جاسوسًا.  يجب أن يكون إطار عمل.
Sister,
أخت،
say something.
قل شيئا.
Mo Xi doesn't know martial arts at all,
مو شي لا يعرف فنون الدفاع عن النفس على الإطلاق ،
how could she be a spy?
كيف تكون جاسوسة؟
Sister,
أخت،
I'm not sure.
لست متأكد.
Who says spies must be good at martial arts?
من قال أن الجواسيس يجب أن يكونوا جيدين في فنون الدفاع عن النفس؟
Sister.
أخت.
Ruoruo Moxi,
رورو موكسي ،
as you said, she's not a spy,
كما قلت ، إنها ليست جاسوسة ،
She should be in danger now.
يجب أن تكون في خطر الآن.
Tian Si Fang,
تيان سي فانغ ،